

MOHAMED REFAAT

XR Software engineer

About Me

I am an XR software engineer with over seven years of experience in developing immersive and interactive games for various platforms. I specialize in Unity, virtual reality. AR. WebVR MR. and mobile games and have worked on high-budget productions for reputable companies. I have a strong grasp of programming and design patterns, as well as a keen eye for UX, art. and gameplay design. I write clean, well-structured, and self-documenting code that is adaptable to project changes. I thrive under pressure and deliver quality work within tight deadlines.

- •
- +971 583044548
- mohammref312@gmail.com
- 0
- linkedin.com/in/mohammref/
- Q
- mohammref.github.io/

Language

- Arabic (Native)
- English

Expertise

- C Sharp (C#)
- Unity 3D, 2D
- Game Development
- Virtual Reality (VR)
- Augmented Reality (AR)
- Mixed Reality (MR)
- WebVR

Experience

XR Software Engineer Ekson - Almotahida Education Mar 2023 - until now

- XR Educational Applications
- unity 3D development

Extended Reality developer IVY Stem International School Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

- virtual Reality Applications
- Augmented reality Applications
- mixed reality Applications
- unity 3D development

Extended Reality developer bright Vision Company Jan 2021 - Oct 2022

- virtual Reality Applications
- Augmented reality application
- unity 3D development
- WebVR

Augmented Reality for educational Mimic

Mar 2020 - Dec 2020

- augmented reality using EasyAR for educational
- unity 3D Applications

Education

Banha University

Bachelor of : Computers and Artificial Intelligence 2015 - 2018

Udacity

Virtual Reality Nanodegree 2017 - 2018

Skills Summary

XR Reality

Game Development

95%

90%